//Questions array

var quizzles = [
  {
    question: "What are the primitive data types in Javascript?",
    choices: ["Boolean, String, Number, Undefined", "String, Number, Undefined, Class", "Boolean, Number, String, Defined", "String, Boolean, Letter, Number"],
    answer: "Boolean, String, Number, Undefined"
},{
    question: "What must be included before a variable's name to declare it as a variable?",
    choices: ["variable", "vari", "var", "vbl"],
    answer: "var"
},{
    question: "How does one fetch an element by id through DOM?",
    choices: ["document.getIdElement", "window.getElementId", "document.getElementById", "document.writeElementbyId"],
    answer: "document.getElementById"
}, {
    question: "How does one create a new function?",
    choices: ["function = myFunction()", "function(myFunction())", "function: myFunction()", "function myFunction()"],
    answer: "function myFunction()"
}, {
    question: "What must be included before a variable's name to declare it as a variable?",
    choices: ["variable", "vari", "var", "vbl"],
    answer: "var"
}, {
    question:"How can one determine if there is strict equality between variables 'a' and 'b'?",
    choices:["a == b", "a =!= b", "a === b", "a = b"],
    answer: "a === b"
}, {
    question:"How can one identify if both expressions are true?",
    choices:["expression1 || expression2", "expression1 =!= expression2", "expression1 && expression2", "expression1 == expression2"],
    answer: "expression1 && expression2"
}, {
    question:"How does one write an array?",
    choices:["<'a', 'b', 'c', 'd'>", "['a', 'b', 'c', 'd'], [a, b, c, d]", "(a, b, c, d)"],
    answer: "['a', 'b', 'c', 'd']"
}, {
    question:"What is the first letter of the Caped Crusader's superhero name?",
    choices:["a", "b", "c", "d"],
    answer: "b"
}, {
    question:"How can one associate a response to an event, like a button being clicked?",
    choices:["Button.listenForEvent('click', function())", "Button.EventListener('click', function())", "Button.addEventListener('click', function())", "Button.listenToEvent('click', function())" ],
    answer: "Button.addEventListener('click', function())"
}]